####   [OnlineGDB beta](https://www.onlinegdb.com/)

online compiler and debugger for c/c++
======================================

code. compile. run. debug. share.

[About](https://www.onlinegdb.com/about) • [FAQ](https://www.onlinegdb.com/faq) • [Blog](https://www.onlinegdb.com/blog/) • [Terms of Use](https://www.onlinegdb.com/termsofuse) • [Contact Us](https://www.onlinegdb.com/contact) • [GDB Tutorial](http://www.gdbtutorial.com/) • [Credits](https://www.onlinegdb.com/credits) • [Privacy](https://www.onlinegdb.com/privacy)

© 2016 - 2024 GDB Online

### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy describes the types of information collected by onlinegdb.com and how it is used.

#### What Information we collect

We might collect user’s personal information such as name, email, social account profile id, ip address, country. We may also collect other information such as date and time stamp of account creation, date and time stamp of recent login to website and other similar information.

#### Different ways to collect information

We collect information directly from you when you register, login or post information via contact form to our website.  
We collect information automatically when you use the services of our website, such as but not limited to when creating shared link of code project.  

#### Use of information

We may use information to verify your account at our website by sending verification email to your registered email address.  
We use information to respond to your questions or requests.  
We use information to improve our products and services. We may use your information to customize your experience with us. This could include displaying content based upon your preferences.  
We use information for security purposes to protect our users and our website. We use information as otherwise permitted by law.

#### What rights you have over your data

You can request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. You can send your request for data deletion at info(a-t)onlinegdb\[d.o.t\]com

#### Disclaimer

The contents of this report are based on information generally available to the public from sources believed to be reliable. No representation is made that it is timely, accurate or complete. OnlineGDB has taken due care and caution in compilation of data as this has been obtained from various sources including which it considers reliable and first hand. However, OnlineGDB does not guarantee the accuracy, adequacy or completeness of any information and it is not responsible for any errors or omissions or for the results obtained from the use of such information and especially states that it has no financial liability whatsoever to the subscribers/users of this report. The information herein, together with all estimates and forecasts, can change without notice. This report does not purport to be a solicitation of any advice pertaining to trade and business and readers are advised to consult experts or study/evaluate individual business prospectus and other relevant legal documents before taking any decisions based on information provided in the site. Neither OnlineGDB nor Admins accept any liability whatsoever nor do they accept responsibility for any financial consequences arising from the use of the research or information provided herein.

#### Privacy Policy

We understand the importance of your privacy as a visitor to this website. We want you to understand how the information you may provide will be used. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

#### Third party websites

We use the services of third party websites such as Google Analytics, Addthis.com, buysellads.com for tracking and ad display purpose. Third party websites may track and collect user data, they may have different privacy policy which can be different from ours. If you click on one of the links to third party websites, you may be taken to websites we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of those websites. Read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third party sites.

#### Jurisdiction

If you choose to visit the website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and the website's terms of use. In addition to the foregoing, any disputes arising under this Policy shall be governed by the laws of India.

#### Changes to this Privacy Statement

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of OnlineGDB then you may contact us through the [contact form](https://www.onlinegdb.com/contact) page.

Best Regards,  
The OnlineGDB Team

×

#### Possible reasons for Runtime Exceed error

1. If your program is reading input from standard input and you forgot to provide input via stdin.
2. Your program contains infinite loop, which may never break.
3. Your program contains infinite recursive function calls.
4. May be your program is trying to process large data and it takes much time to process

ok

×

Ok

×

#### New Version Available

New Version of OnlineGDB is available. Please save your data and refresh page to update.

Ok

×

#### Running Turbo C Project

×

#### Save Project

Name of Project: 

**Destination Folder**   Change

Save

×

#### Extra Compiler Flags

Ok

×

#### Are you sure you want to delete file \`\`?

Yes No

×

Yes No

×

#### New File

Name of new file: 

ok

×

#### Rename File

Name: 

ok cancel

×

#### Share Link

source code is copied to below link.

×

#### Lost connection to server

Oops! Connection to server is lost. Please refresh the page to reconnect.

ok

×

#### Debug session stopped

Debug session is being stopped due to inactivity.

ok

×

#### Debug mode for python program is not yet supported.

ok

×

#### Login to your account

### Login with

×

#### Run Console session stopped

Run Console is being stopped due to inactivity.

ok

×

#### Add School/University/Institute

School/University/Institute Name\* 

State\* 

Country\* Select Country

Close Submit

×

#### Keyboard Shortcuts

**IDE Shortcuts:**
New file : Ctrl-M
Run Code : F9
Debug Code : F8
Save Project : Ctrl-S
Beautify Code : Ctrl-B
Settings Menu : Ctrl-Shift-S
Info : Ctrl-I

**Editor Shortcuts:**
showSettingsMenu : Ctrl-,
goToNextError : Alt-E
goToPreviousError : Alt-Shift-E
selectall : Ctrl-A
gotoline : Ctrl-L
fold : Alt-L|Ctrl-F1
unfold : Alt-Shift-L|Ctrl-Shift-F1
toggleFoldWidget : F2
toggleParentFoldWidget : Alt-F2
foldOther : Alt-0
unfoldall : Alt-Shift-0
findnext : Ctrl-K
findprevious : Ctrl-Shift-K
selectOrFindNext : Alt-K
selectOrFindPrevious : Alt-Shift-K
find : Ctrl-F
overwrite : Insert
selecttostart : Ctrl-Shift-Home
gotostart : Ctrl-Home
selectup : Shift-Up
golineup : Up
selecttoend : Ctrl-Shift-End
gotoend : Ctrl-End
selectdown : Shift-Down
golinedown : Down
selectwordleft : Ctrl-Shift-Left
gotowordleft : Ctrl-Left
selecttolinestart : Alt-Shift-Left
gotolinestart : Alt-Left|Home
selectleft : Shift-Left
gotoleft : Left
selectwordright : Ctrl-Shift-Right
gotowordright : Ctrl-Right
selecttolineend : Alt-Shift-Right
gotolineend : Alt-Right|End
selectright : Shift-Right
gotoright : Right
selectpagedown : Shift-Pagedown
gotopagedown : Pagedown
selectpageup : Shift-Pageup
gotopageup : Pageup
scrollup : Ctrl-Up
scrolldown : Ctrl-Down
selectlinestart : Shift-Home
selectlineend : Shift-End
togglerecording : Ctrl-Alt-E
replaymacro : Ctrl-Shift-E
jumptomatching : Ctrl-P
selecttomatching : Ctrl-Shift-P
expandToMatching : Ctrl-Shift-M
removeline : Ctrl-D
duplicateSelection : Ctrl-Shift-D
sortlines : Ctrl-Alt-S
togglecomment : Ctrl-/
toggleBlockComment : Ctrl-Shift-/
modifyNumberUp : Ctrl-Shift-Up
modifyNumberDown : Ctrl-Shift-Down
replace : Ctrl-H
undo : Ctrl-Z
redo : Ctrl-Shift-Z|Ctrl-Y
copylinesup : Alt-Shift-Up
movelinesup : Alt-Up
copylinesdown : Alt-Shift-Down
movelinesdown : Alt-Down
del : Delete
backspace : Shift-Backspace|Backspace
cut\_or\_delete : Shift-Delete
removetolinestart : Alt-Backspace
removetolineend : Alt-Delete
removewordleft : Ctrl-Backspace
removewordright : Ctrl-Delete
outdent : Shift-Tab
indent : Tab
blockoutdent : Ctrl-\[
blockindent : Ctrl-\]
transposeletters : Ctrl-T
touppercase : Ctrl-U
tolowercase : Ctrl-Shift-U
expandtoline : Ctrl-Shift-L
addCursorAbove : Ctrl-Alt-Up
addCursorBelow : Ctrl-Alt-Down
addCursorAboveSkipCurrent : Ctrl-Alt-Shift-Up
addCursorBelowSkipCurrent : Ctrl-Alt-Shift-Down
selectMoreBefore : Ctrl-Alt-Left
selectMoreAfter : Ctrl-Alt-Right
selectNextBefore : Ctrl-Alt-Shift-Left
selectNextAfter : Ctrl-Alt-Shift-Right
splitIntoLines : Ctrl-Alt-L
alignCursors : Ctrl-Alt-A
findAll : Ctrl-Alt-K
showKeyboardShortcuts : Ctrl-Alt-H

Close
